[
  {
    "question": "When was minecraft released?",
    "answers": ["2011", "2009", "2002"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many blocks are in a chunk?",
    "answers": ["256", "200", "64"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these components is not in a Kinect.V1?",
    "answers": ["Banana", "Color sensor", "IR depth sensor"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A polygonal mesh is:",
    "answers": ["A collection of polygons satisfying certain restrictions", "Macintosh Enhanced SCSI Hardware", "A very famous cocktail"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A triangle mesh is called manifold if the intersection of two triangles is",
    "answers": ["A common vertex", "Full", "Colorful"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is defined as sum of translated and scaled kernels and a linear polynomial?",
    "answers": ["Radial Basis Function", "Eminem mom's spaghetti", "Signed Distance Function"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What we always need in order to obtain actual depth data?",
    "answers": ["Two optical centers", "A dimond pickaxe", "The enchanting table"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Structure from Motion:",
    "answers": ["recover both 3D points and camera positions", "Is never gonna give you up", "Is never gonna let you down"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What SLAM stands for?",
    "answers": ["Simultaneous Localization and Mapping", "When one team in the Six Nations Championship beats all the others during one year's competition.", "A sweet jam"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What you DON'T need to align two objects using known correspondences?",
    "answers": ["A ruler", "Compute center of gravity of both objects", "Scale one object to match the avg. distance from all vertices to the center of gravity"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In which year was the 'famous' game 'The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time' released?",
    "answers": ["1996", "1998", "2001"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the protagonist in the game 'Assasin's Creed'?",
    "answers": ["Ezio Auditore", "Connor Kenway", "Altair Ibn-La'Ahad"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these games is developed by the software house CD Projekt?",
    "answers": ["The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt", "Fallout 4", "Grand Theft Auto V"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main genre of the game 'League of Legends'?",
    "answers": ["Multiplayer online battle arena (MOBA)", "First-person shooter (FPS)", "Role-playing game (RPG)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the creator of the famous game 'Minecraft'?",
    "answers": ["Markus Persson", "Hideo Kojima", "Shigeru Miyamoto"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In which year was the PlayStation 4 console from Sony launched?",
    "answers": ["2013", "2011", "2015"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the title of the first game in the 'Final Fantasy' series?",
    "answers": ["Final Fantasy I", "Titanic", "Nokia 3310"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not a playable character in 'Super Smash Bros. Ultimate'?",
    "answers": ["Mario", "Master Chief", "Donkey Kong"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the protagonist in the game 'The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim'?",
    "answers": ["Dovahkiin", "Geralt of Rivia", "Nathan Drake"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which game development studio created the 'Uncharted' series?",
    "answers": ["Naughty Dog", "Rockstar Games", "Bethesda Game Studios"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which option is not a Deformation Proxy?",
    "answers": ["Ghosts", "Cages", "Skeletons"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Find the only Corrispondence Pruning Strategy",
    "answers": ["Distance", "Sacking", "Slicing"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Non-rigid Tracking is more stable with:",
    "answers": ["More cameras", "Less cameras", "A good motivational speech"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Non-rigid Reconstruction can accumulate ... if traking is wrong",
    "answers": ["drift", "drag", "dandruff"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is not an indipendent PCA in the Morphable Model?",
    "answers": ["Beauty", "Identity", "Albedo"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the name of the technique used to enhance the realism of generated 3D scans in computer vision, involving a competition between a generator and a discriminator network?",
    "answers": ["Adversarial Loss", "Spatial Filtering", "Touching grass"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Standard Skinning produces vertices from...",
    "answers": ["Pose parameters", "T-pose", "Pole position"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Best F1 team?",
    "answers": ["Ferrari", "Wrong option", "Wrong option"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you are happy and you know it, ...",
    "answers": ["clap your hands", "run away", "ask for help"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The best project in the world is...",
    "answers": ["This one", "Another one", "Somebody please help me I'm stuck in a quiz factory!"]
  }
]